ACON is optimized for viewing in Chrome.

Don't show for 30 days

Don't show for 30 days

Personal Information Processing Policy

**chPersonal Information Handling Policy**
==========================================

<Personal information handler: Lee Min-hong\] > Personal Information Handling Policy

Carpenstreet Inc. (hereinafter referred to as ‘the Company’) attaches great importance to protecting users’ personal information and is doing its best to ensure that the personal information provided to the Company online while using the Company’s services is protected.

Accordingly, the Company complies with the personal information protection regulations of relevant laws and regulations that information and communication service providers, including the Communications Secrets Protection Act, Telecommunications Business Act, Act on Promotion of Information and Communications Network Utilization and Information Protection, etc., must comply with, and the personal information protection guidelines established by the Ministry of Information and Communication.

Through the Personal Information Handling Policy, the Company provides users with a clear understanding of the purpose and method for which the personal information they provide is being used. We also detail the comprehensive measures taken to protect personal information, ensuring transparency and user awareness.

The Company values transparency and therefore, the Personal Information Handling Policy is prominently disclosed on its website's first screen. This ensures that users can easily access and review it at any time, fostering a sense of being well-informed.

The Company's Personal Information Handling Policy is designed to adapt to changes when necessary. This includes changes in government laws and guidelines or changes in the Company's internal policies. Rest assured, necessary procedures are in place to continuously improve the Personal Information Handling Policy, instilling confidence in our users.

In addition, if the Personal Information Handling Policy is revised or if there are any changes, notification will be prominently displayed through the Personal Information Handling Policy on the front page of the service website. We strongly advise users to check the Policy frequently when visiting the website to stay updated.

The Company's Personal Information Handling Policy contains the following:

1\. Consent to the collection of personal information;

2\. Purpose of processing personal information;

3\. Processing and retention period of personal information;

4\. Sharing and provision of collected personal information;

5\. Rights/obligations and exercise methods of information subjects and legal representatives;

6\. Personal information items processed;

7\. Destruction of personal information;

8\. Measures to ensure the safety of personal information;

9\. Matters related to installation/operation and refusal of automatic personal information collection devices;

10\. Personal information protection officer;

11\. Request to access personal information;

12\. Remedy for infringement of rights and interests;

13\. Changes to the Personal Information Handling Policy

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, establishes/discloses the Personal Information Handling Policy as follows to protect the personal information of information owners in accordance with Article 30 of the <Personal Information Protection Act> and to quickly and smoothly handle complaints related thereto.

**Article 1 (Consent to the collection of personal information)**
-----------------------------------------------------------------

The Company establishes a procedure for users to click “Agree” to the Company’s Personal Information Handling Policy or Terms of Use. By clicking the “Agree” button, the user is deemed to have consented to the collection of personal information by the Company.

**Article 2 (Purpose of processing personal information)**
==========================================================

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, handles personal information for the following purposes. Personal information being handled will not be used for purposes other than the following. If the purpose of use changes, necessary measures shall be taken, such as obtaining separate consent in accordance with Article 18 of the Personal Information Protection Act.

1\. Membership registration and rights on the website

Personal information is handled for the following purposes: confirmation of intention to become a member, identification/authentication of a person according to the provision of membership service, maintenance/management of membership, prevention of illegal use of service, confirmation of legal representative's consent when handling the personal information of children under 14 years of age, various notices/notifications, and grievance handling.

2\. Provision of goods or services

Personal information is handled for the following purposes: fulfillment of agreements, provision of services, contract/invoice sending, provision of content, guidance on new services and new products or event information, provision of customized services, identity verification, age verification, bill payment/settlement, and debt collection.

The Company can develop more useful services based on personal information provided by users. In addition, when developing new services or expanding content, the Company can more efficiently prioritize the services to be developed based on the personal information provided to the Company by registered users and reasonably select and deliver the content that users need.

3\. Grievance handling

Personal information is handled for the following purposes: verification of the identity of the person seeking services, confirmation of the requested services, contact/notification for factual investigation and information, securing a smooth communication path for affair handling, and notification of the result of handling.

**Article 3 (Processing and retention period of personal information)**
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

1\. Lee Min-hong, designated to handle personal information, handles/retains personal information within the retention/use period of personal information pursuant to the law or within the personal information retention/use period agreed upon when collecting personal information from the information owner. While users use the services provided by the Company as members, the Company continues to retain users' personal information and uses it to provide services, etc. However, if the member deletes or modifies information or requests cancellation of membership in accordance with the procedures and methods described in Article 7 (Destruction of Personal Information), the information will be destroyed.

2\. For each case, the handling and retention period of personal information is as follows.

1) Registration and management of service memberships: Until withdrawal from the business/organization website;

In the case of the following reasons, until the end of the relevant reason:

a) If an investigation is in progress for violation of relevant laws and regulations, until the end of the investigation

b) If any claims/debt relationships remain due to use of the website, until the relevant claims/debt relationships are settled

c) In case of <exception reasons>, until the <retention period>

2) Provision of goods or services: Until completion of supply of goods/services and completion of payment/settlement;

In the following cases, until the end of the relevant period:

a) Records of transactions, such as labeling/advertising, contract details, and performance, in accordance with the Act on Consumer Protection in Electronic Commerce, etc.

b) Records of labeling/advertising: 6 months;

c) Records of contract or subscription cancellation, payment, supply of goods, etc.: Until the service is terminated;

d) Records of processing consumer complaints or disputes: 3 years;

e) Communication data in accordance with the Communication Secrets Protection Act;

f) Subscriber's telecommunication date and time, start/end time, other party's subscriber number, frequency of use, location tracking data from the source base station: 1 year

g) Computer communication, Internet log records, access point tracking data: 3 months

h) Temporary purposes (surveys, events, identity verification, etc.): Destroyed after achieving the purpose.

**Article 4 (Sharing and provision of collected personal information)**
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

The Company uses users' personal information within the scope notified in Article 2 and does not use it beyond this scope or, in principle, disclose users' personal information to a third party without the user's prior consent, excluding the following cases:

1\. When the user consents to disclosure in advance;

2\. When it is necessary to settle fees for service provision;

3\. When the user violates the terms of use or operating principles of the service terms and conditions and other member services posted on the website;

4\. When there are sufficient grounds to believe that personal information must be disclosed to take legal action against a user who causes mental or material damage to others by using our service;

5\. When it is judged in good faith that it is required by other laws (e.g., when there is a request from the government/investigative agency through legal procedures in accordance with relevant laws, etc.) ;

6\. When personal information is provided to advertisers, partners, or research organizations in a form that does not identify specific individuals for statistical purposes, academic research, or market research;

**Article 5 (Rights/obligations and exercise methods of information owners and legal representatives)**
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1\. The information owner may exercise the right to view/correct/delete/stop handling personal information at any time to Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information.

2\. Users may exercise their rights, as outlined in Paragraph 1, to Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, by submitting a written request, sending an e-mail, or using other forms of communication such as facsimile (FAX) in accordance with Article 41, Paragraph 1 of the Enforcement Decree of the Personal Information Protection Act. After recognizing such requests, Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, shall take action without delay.

3\. If desired, users may view their personal information within the Company's service at any time.

4\. Users can modify the stored essential information and view, edit, or delete some additional information other than the required information when registering as a member. Users can change or delete personal information and withdraw membership after logging in to the Company's My Page.

5\. The information owner may exercise the rights under Paragraph 1 by delegating the right to a legal representative or agent. In this case, the person to whom the rights have been delegated must submit power of attorney in accordance with the form in Appendix 11 of the Notice on How to Handle Personal Information (No. 2020-7).

6\. The information owner's right to view and stop handling personal information may be limited by Article 35, Paragraph 4 and Article 37, Paragraph 2 of the Personal Information Protection Act.

7\. The information owner cannot request correction or deletion for personal information that is specified as the subject of collection in other laws and regulations.

8\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, confirms whether the person making the request, such as a request for viewing, correction/deletion, or suspension of handling according to the rights of the information owner, is the person or a legitimate agent.

**Article 6 (Personal information items handled)**
--------------------------------------------------

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, handles personal information items, including:

1\. Registration and management of service membership;

1) General members

| General registration |     | Required: email, password, name, mobile phone number, related occupation |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Social sign-in | Google | Required: email, name, mobile phone number, related occupation, profile photo, unique identifier |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Naver | Required: email, name, mobile phone number, related occupation, unique identifier |
| --- | --- | --- |

2) Seller members

2-1) Individual members in Korea

\- Required: ID (email), password, name, resident registration number, brand name, contact information, store review materials

2-2) Business members in Korea

\- Required: ID (email), password, business name, CEO's name, business type, business registration number, brand name, contact information, store review materials

2-3) Members outside of Korea

\- Required: ID (email), password, name, country of residence, brand name, contact information, store review materials

\- Optional: tax identification number

2\. Provision of goods or services;

1) General members

\- Required: name, date of birth, ID, password, address, phone number, email address, credit card number, bank account information

\- Optional: areas of interest, history of purchase records

2) Seller members

2-1) Individual members in Korea

\- Required: copy of ID, copy of bankbook, name of account holder, bank, account number

\- Optional: none

2-2) Business members in Korea

\- Required: copy of business registration certificate, copy of bankbook, name of account holder, bank, account number

\- Optional: none

2-3) Members outside of Korea

\- Required: copy of ID, application for reduced tax rate, account type, account address

\- Optional: none

3\. Personal information items, including IP address, cookie, MAC address, service use record, and visit record, may be automatically created and collected while using Internet services.

**Article 7 (Destruction of personal information)**
---------------------------------------------------

1\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, destroys personal information without delay when it becomes unnecessary, such as when the personal information retention period has elapsed or when the purpose of handling has been achieved.

2\. Even if the personal information retention period agreed to by the information owner has elapsed or the purpose of handling has been achieved, if the personal information must continue to be preserved in accordance with other laws and regulations, it will be transferred to a separate database (DB) or preserved in another storage location.

\- Personal information items to be preserved: ID, transaction date, handle, business/team name, project name

3\. Personal information is destroyed through the following procedures and methods.

\- Destruction procedures

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, selects personal information that is subject to destruction and destroys personal information with the approval of the personal information protection officer.

\- Destruction methods

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, destroys personal information recorded/saved in electronic files in a non-recoverable manner and destroys personal information recorded/saved in paper documents by shredding or incineration.

**Article 8 (Measures to ensure the safety of personal information)**
---------------------------------------------------------------------

Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, takes measures to ensure the safety of personal information by:

1\. Management measures: establishment and implementation of internal management plan, regular employee training, etc.;

2\. Technical measures: Management of access rights such as personal information handling systems, installation of access control systems, encryption of unique identification information, etc., installation of security programs

**Article 9 (Matters related to installation/operation and refusal of automatic personal information collection devices)**

1\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, uses 'cookies' to store usage information and retrieve it periodically to provide individualized services to users.

2\. Cookies are small amounts of information that the server (HTTP) uses to operate the website, and software sends to the user's computer browser and stores on the hard disk of the user's PC.

\- The purpose of cookies is to provide optimized information to users by identifying visit and usage patterns, popular search terms, and secure access to each service and website the user visits.

3\. Users may refuse to store cookies through option settings in the Tools>Internet Options>Personal Information menu at the top of the web browser. If the user refuses to store cookies on the website, difficulties may arise in using customized services. If the user refuses to store cookies in the software, the software cannot be installed or used. Users who refuse to store cookies may have difficulty using customized services.

**Article 10 (Provision of personal information to third parties)**
-------------------------------------------------------------------

1\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, handles the personal information of the information owner only within the scope specified in Article 2 (Purpose of handling personal information) and provides personal information to third parties only in cases that fall under Articles 17 and 18 of the Personal Information Protection Act, including the consent of the information owner and special provisions of the law.

2\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, provides personal information to third parties as follows.

1) For stores that have signed an agreement with the Company

\- Purpose of use of personal information of the recipient: Confirmation of purchase and settlement details

\- Personal information items provided: pen name/team name, project name, order/payment date and time, purchase product information

\- Period of retention/use by recipient: Until information is destroyed

**Article 11 (Entrustment of handling personal information)**
-------------------------------------------------------------

1\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, entrusts personal information handling as follows to ensure efficient and safe personal information processing.

1) PG companies that entered an agreement with the Company

• Trustees: KG Inicis, Payletter, Allpay, PortOne, Toss Payments, EximBay, PayPal, Payoneer Inc., Daou Data

• Entrusted work: Payment service

2) Service operators that entered an agreement with the Company

• Trustees: Amazon Web Services Inc., Megazone Cloud, Microsoft Azure, Mixpanel, Sentry, Metabase, Microsoft Power BI, Datadog, Google Cloud, Dow Data, Epic Games, MODUSIGN, Hotjar Ltd., Danal

• Entrusted work: Data storage and analysis, AWS service operation, contract processing, user authentication

3) Marketing operators that entered an agreement with the Company

• Trustees: Stibeee, Aligo, Grey Box, SendGrid

• Entrusted work: Email, Kakao Notification Talk, Kakao Friend Talk, text messages

2\. When concluding an entrustment agreement, Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, supervises whether each trustee handles personal information safely and specifies prohibition on handling personal information other than to perform consignment work, technical/managerial protection measures, restrictions on re-entrustment, management supervision of the trustee, compensation for damages, etc., matters related to responsibility in documents such as contracts in accordance with Article 26 of the Personal Information Protection Act.

3\. Any changes in the details of the entrusted work or the trustee shall be disclosed without delay through this Personal Information Handling Policy.

**Article 12 (Personal information protection officer)**
--------------------------------------------------------

1\. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, appoints a personal information protection officer who takes overall responsibility for the work related to \*\*\*\* personal information processing, handling complaints, and providing relief for damage to information owners related to personal information processing.

\- Name of the personal information protection officer: Lee Minhong

Position: Development Officer

Contact: minhong@acon3d.com

\- Department of Personal Information Protection: Personal Information TF, Manager: Seo Jung-soo

Contact: julie@acon3d.com

2\. The information owner may contact the personal information protection officer and the responsible department for all personal information protection-related inquiries, complaint handling, damage relief, etc., that arise while using the service of Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, shall promptly respond to and investigate the information owner's inquiries.

**Article 13 (Request to access personal information)**
-------------------------------------------------------

The information owner may request access to his or her personal information pursuant to Article 35 of the Personal Information Protection Act to the department below. Lee Min-hong, the person designated to handle personal information, shall make every effort to promptly process the information owner's request to access the personal information.

\- Department of processing personal information access requests: Personal Information TF

Officer: Lee Minhong

Contact: minhong@acon3d.com

**Article 14 (Remedy for infringement of rights and interests)**
----------------------------------------------------------------

To receive relief from personal information infringement, the information owner may apply for dispute resolution or consult with the Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee or the Korea Internet & Security Agency's Personal Information Infringement Reporting Center. Please contact the organizations below for other personal information infringement reports and consultations.

1) Personal Information Dispute Mediation Committee: (No Area Code) 1833-6972 (www.kopico.go.kr)

2) Personal Information Infringement Reporting Center: (No Area Code) 118 (privacy.kisa.or.kr)

3) Supreme Prosecutors' Office: (No Area Code) 1301 (www.spo.go.kr)

4) National Police Agency: (No Area Code) 182 (cyberbureau.police.go.kr)

Regarding requests pursuant to the provisions of the Personal Information Protection Act, Article 35 (Access to Personal Information), Article 36 (Correction and Deletion of Personal Information), and Article 37 (Suspension of Processing of Personal Information, etc.), an information owner whose rights or interests have been infringed due to a disposition or omission by the head of a public institution may request an administrative trial in accordance with the Administrative Appeals Act.

For more information about administrative appeals, please refer to the Central Administrative Appeals Commission (www.simpan.go.kr) website.

**Article 15 (Changes to the Personal Information Handling Policy)**
--------------------------------------------------------------------

This Personal Information Handling Policy is effective from December 09, 2024.

한국어English中文日本語

Company: carpenstreet Inc.

Representative: Minhong Daniel Lee

Address: 7F, 27, Eonju-ro 93-gil, Gangnam-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea

Mail order business registration number: 2021-SeoulGangnam-04401

KOR Business Registration Number: 364-87-01374 KOR Business information confirmation >

Personal Information Manager: Minhong Daniel Lee

Contact: cs@acon3d.com

Hosting provided by NHN godo

copyright (c) www.acon3d.com all rights reserved.
